Ismay, Lou; Papers ua902.064
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Student Writings, 1969-1977; Undated; 4; 11.75 cubic ft.
  - Sims, Richard, The use of Res Ipsa Loquitus in Medical Malpractice Cases, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 14)
  - Skorulski, Susan, Thermal Pollution: A heated Issue, 1974 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 15)
  - Sloman, Susan, Environmental Impact Statements and Computer Simulation, 1975 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 16)
  - Smith, Cheryl, Environmental Protection, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 17)
  - Smith, Godfrey; Metayer, Gary; A General Report on the Surface Mining and Land Reclamation Project, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 18)
  - Snitowsky, Steven, Lead Poisoning, 1974 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 19)
  - Snyder, Bill, et al. Trail Mapping, 1972 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 20)
  - Sociology 457, 1972 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 21)
  - Saffler, Joyce, Summaries, 1970 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 22)
  - Sollazzo, John, The Monk Parakeet, Friend or Foe?, 1973 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 23)
  - Soloman, Amy; Richter, Laurie Pethood or Parenthood, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 24)
  - Sorgen, Larry, Slides, 1973 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 25)
  - Sorgen, Lawrence; McMahon, Brian Noise Pollution, 1972 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 26)
  - Soroka, Sharon, Forgotten Americans: Words and Pictures, 1970 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 27)
  - Spiegel, Jeffrey, The Eagle: Death of a National Symbol, 1975 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 28)
  - Spivack, Allen, Here Comes De'sludge: A Study in Water Dumping Management, 1974 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 29)
  - Spivack, Allan, Log, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 30)
  - Spivack, Allan, NYS Standing Committee an Environmental Conservation, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 31)
  - Spivack, Allan, A Time to Choose: An Analysis of Energy Alternatives for NY State, 1976 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 32)
  - Spizzo V., The Process of Digestion, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 33)
  - Staccone, Matthew ,Report on Environmental Education in the Legislature, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 34)
  - Staccone, Matthew, untitled, 1977 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 35)
  - Stanley, Bill, Consumerism -- What's it all About?, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 36)
  - Stap, Lorie, Nuclear Power Plants on Long Island, 1975 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 37)
  - Stein, Jeffrey, Music and Environment, 1971 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 38)
  - Steinert, James, Composting in a Solid Waste Management Program, 1971 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 39)
  - Stern, Gary, the Overall Effect of Surface Mining on American Society, 1974 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 40)
  - Stewart, John, The Reserve Clause and Curt Flood, 1972 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 41)
  - Stewart, Paul, Champlain Canal House Project Report, 1974 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 42)
  - Stewart, Paul; Jackson, Lynne An Introduction to Moss Island, 1974 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 43)
  - Stock, Nancy, Weather Control, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 44)
  - Stopal, Larry, Prisoners Rights and Penal Conditions, 1973 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 45)
  - Stransman, Jill; Sigberman, Richard; Koval, Andret; Healthy Foods, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 46)
  - Strudler, Michael, untitled, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 47)
  - Stuart, John, Nuclear Power in NY State, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 48)
  - Sugarman, Joel, The Hazards of Chemical Pest Control, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 49)
  - Swartz, Jane, Love Sex and Birth Control for the mentally Retarded, 1974 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 50)
  - Sylvester, Michael; Sherwin, Bruce; Giordano, Tom; Energy Alternatives for the Future: Solar Power, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 51)
  - Symansky, Bonnie, Log, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 52)
  - Szabo, Victoria, Overview of U.S. Population Policies; Time for a Change?, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 53)
  - Szabo, Victoria, Noise Assessment in Community Development Areas, 1975 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 54)
  - Taldone, Nicholas, Why We Need A Bottle Bill, 1975 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 55)
  - Tatro, Susen Marie, A Study of Endangered Species of Mammals, 1972 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 56)
  - Taubman, Ed; Shenn, Fred; untitled, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 57)
  - Telvar, Jan, untitled, 1972 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 58)
  - Testo, Joseph, Home Application of Alternative Energy, 1976 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 59)
  - Testo, Joseph, Journal, 1977 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 60)
  - Testo, Joseph, Solar Home Design, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 61)
  - Thailer, Rich; Weiner, Perry; Slides, 1976 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 62)
  - Thailer, Richard; Weiner, Perry; untitled, 1976 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 63)
  - Thayer, Anita, Independent Study, 1971 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 64)
  - Thomas, Herbert, Problems within our Environment, 1971 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 65)
  - Thomson, Steven, Fear and threat Arousal and their Effects on Atitude Change, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 66)
  - Tobin, Lynn, Albany Sanitation, 1972 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 67)
  - Toder, Jordan, Environmental Exposure of Toxic Substances, 1976 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 68)
  - Toffolo, Diana, The Solar Energy Alternative, 1977 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 69)
  - Tracy, Jerome, Whale Protection: Enough?, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 70)
  - Tremblay, Joseph, Various uses of Solar Energy, 1975 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 71)
  - Tripodi, Joe, Flouridation Report, 1976 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 72)
  - Tuchman, Robert, Students as they Should be; Leaders not the Led, 1973 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 73)
  - Tuchman, Vicki, Red Tide, 1973 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 74)
  - Tundat, William, The World Food Problem, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 75)
  - Turnbull, Paul, Resource Management of the Coastal Zone, 1974 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 76)
  - Tymann, Jeffrey, Law & Society, 1972 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 77)
  - Unnamed 1805 Map Overlay, 1973 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 1)
  - Unnamed Air Pollution, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 2)
  - Unnamed Earthday Survey, 1970 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 3)
  - Unnamed Foot Trails, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 4)
  - Unamed Help!, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 5)
  - Unnamed Human Ecology and Community, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 6)
  - Unnamed Indian and Oriental Views of Nature and Themselves, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 7)
  - Unnamed The Injustices to Blacks in the U.S. Penal System, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 8)
  - Unnamed Journal, 1974 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 9)
  - Unnamed Journal, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 10)
  - Unnamed Maps of bike Trails, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 11)
  - Unnamed Photographs, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 12-14)
  - Unamed A Planters Guide, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 15)
  - Unnamed Slides, 1976 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 16)
  - Unnamed Slides, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 17)
  - Unnamed Thermal Water Pollution, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 18)
  - Unnamed Tuna Survey, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 19)
  - Unnamed, untitled, 1971 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 20)
  - Unnamed, Untitled, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 21-29)
  - Unnamed, Water Pollution, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 30)
  - Unnamed, The Youth Influence in Society, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 31)
  - Van Cott, JoAnn Some Thoughts on Womankind, 1971 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 32)
  - Van Wagenen, R.S. New York State Wild Life Policy -- Is it Sound?, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 33)
  - Vanini, Michale; Bass, Ronald; Bicycle Routes in Albany County, Massachusetts, and Vermont, 1974 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 34)
  - Varney, Christine, Increasing Pollution Awareness: Student Reactions, 1976 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 35)
  - Vein, Robert; Comito, Ronald; Lead Poisoning and Lead Pollution and its Effects on Man and his Environment, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 36)
  - Vota, Wendy, behind Wounded Knee, 1973 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 37)
  - Wade, John, The Nature Conservancy, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 38)
  - Wager, Eileen; Dembroff, Hillary; Developments on the GE Project, 1972 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 39)
  - Wager, Gary, Thermal Pollution, 1975 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 40)
  - Wain, Jeffrey, The Alaskan Pipeline: A Summary, 1975 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 41)
  - Waizola, Gary, Log, 1977 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 42)
  - Walker, Harrison; Blumenthal, Robert; An Alternative Energy Source: Geothermal Power, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 43)
  - Walker, Harrison; Bluementhal, Robert; A Study of racetrack Beautification, 1976 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 44)
  - Walsh, Robert, Pavement =Progress?, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 45)
  - Walters, Michael, The Stock Outflies the American Eagle, 1973 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 46)
  - Warren, P., Repost on EnCon Committee, 1976 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 47)
  - Warren, Suzanne, The Commune called "The Family", 1971 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 48)
  - Warzala, Gary, Planning a Childrens Exhibit at the Schenectady Museum, 1977 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 49)
  - Waterman, Paul, A General Survey on Noise & The Concorde Issue at Present, 1977 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 50)
  - Weber, Jeffrey, Utilization of Kitchen Refuse, 1973 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 51)
  - Weinberg, Ileen, Dorms and Grades, 1976 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 52)
  - Weiner, Felice, This is the Forest Primeval Some Thoughts on Cigarettes, 1970 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 53)
  - Weiner, Howard, Reflections on Mocassins, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 54)
  - Weinstein, Barry, Narrative, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 55)
  - Weinstock, Craig, Environmental Law, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 56)
  - Weiss, Carole, untitled, 1975 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 57)
  - Weitz, Holly, Consumer Report: Long Distance Moving, 1972 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 58)
  - Weitzman, Nancy; Fagen, Michael; Returnable Bottles vs. Non-Returnable Bottles, 1976 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 59)
  - Wesley, Dick, Report, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 60)
  - Westphal, Karl, First Sheet, 1971 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 61)
  - Whisenand, Jim, Directed Readings in Sociology, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 62)
  - Whisenand, Jim, What's Happening at Mont Plasant High School, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 63)
  - Whittingham, Jeffrey A Discourse on Some Ramifications of Law and Philosophy, 1972 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 64)
  - Wiener, William, Pine Bush Report, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 65)
  - Williams, Kerry, Ann Consumer Pollution, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 66)
  - Willis, Amy, The Concept of Space: Its Implications for the urban Environment, 1977 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 67)
  - Wladyka, Steve, Mercury Pollution and its Effect on Man, 1971 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 68)
  - Woodard, Alan, The Consaulus Vly, 1976 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 69)
  - Worden, Melissa, Aircraft Noise, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 70)
  - Wozniak, Edward, Independent Study, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 71)
  - Wozniak, E., Water Pollution: An Overview, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 72)
  - Wright, Richard, Case for No -- Fault, 1972 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 73)
  - Wukitsch, Paul, Experiences of an Aspiring Fiddler, 1976 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 74)
  - Wukitsch, Paul, Waste in the American Diet, 1975 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 75)
  - Wylie, Norah, untitled, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 76)
  - Yablonski, Diane, An Experiment on the Effectiveness of Achillea Millefoliumasan Oral Contraceptive, 1977 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 77)
  - Yablonski, Diane, Oral Contraceptives: Natures Way, 1977 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 78)
  - Yager, Judy, Paper Recycling, 1973 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 79)
  - Zeiger, Alan; Sachs, Bruce; Are The Residence Halls an Academic Environment, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 80)
  - Ziemba, Russ; Ryan, Mike; Sullivan, Frank; Lumber and scrap wood recycling the Economic and Environmental Aspects, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 81)
  - Zinman, Lois, Oil Pollution, Undated (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 82)
  - Zucker, Joel, The Law of Space, 1973 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 83)
  - Zwingle, Erla, Cities and the Crush, 1971 (Box 11 (4-Student Writings), Folder 84)
  - DeGennaro, Ellen; Pickard, Keith; Stoller, Jon; Teevan, Jan; Comparative Agriculture, 1972 (Box 12 (4-Student Writings), Folder 1)
  - DiNova, Jean; Larkin, Rob; Keleshian, George; Horse Trails in the Pine Bush, Undated (Box 12 (4-Student Writings), Folder 2)
  - Flamm, Scott; Schulberg, Francine; Mohawk River Survey, 1976 (Box 12 (4-Student Writings), Folder 3)
  - Goldezer, Susan, Urban Studies: The Family -- Kinship, Undated (Box 12 (4-Student Writings), Folder 4)
  - Hallander, Benni The Effects of Hydrocarbon Emissions from the GE Selkirk Plastic Plant on Plant and Animal Life, 1973 (Box 12 (4-Student Writings), Folder 5)
  - Holland, Mark; Brauner, Andrew; The Trans-Alaskan Pipeline, 1973 (Box 12 (4-Student Writings), Folder 6)
  - Kowalchyk, Joh,n Plants, 1976 (Box 12 (4-Student Writings), Folder 7)
  - Marcus, Ira, Log of Field Trips, 1975 (Box 12 (4-Student Writings), Folder 8)
  - Panson, Rick, Interstate 88 & NYSDOT, 1975 (Box 12 (4-Student Writings), Folder 9)
  - Perecman, David, The Truth About Net Weights, Undated (Box 12 (4-Student Writings), Folder 10)
  - Plecan, Barbara, Bills with Environmental Implications, 1971 (Box 12 (4-Student Writings), Folder 11)
  - Schaber, Michael, Industrial Noise, 1974 (Box 12 (4-Student Writings), Folder 12)
  - Unnamed, Report on Open Space Study City of Albany, Undated (Box 12 (4-Student Writings), Folder 13)
  - Armstrong, Michael, Untitled, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
  - Berland, Larry; Rosenberg, Alex, "Cross Tabulations", 1974 (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - Bortok, Mary, Untitled, 1970 (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
  - Schwartz, Siva; Warren, Marc, "Albany Slums: A Pictorial Essay...", 1971 (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
  - Siskel, Margie, Untitled, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified Student, "Save the Children", Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Student, Untitled, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 7-9)
  - Audiovisuals, 4.821
    - Cohan, Michael; Maccabee, Bob; Liberman, Mitch, Interview with Dr. Aulenbach and Dr. Stross, Audiocassette Tape, 1976 October 25; 1976 November 12 (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
    - Dotz, Robin, Untitled, Audiocassette Tape, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
    - Katz, Jeff, "Where do the Children Play", Audiocassette Tape, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
    - Lipke, Shelley, Untitled, Audiocassette Tape, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
    - Schechter, Steven, "The Population Crisis and Decreasing Food Supplies", Film Reel and paper description, 1973 (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
    - Selwyn, Gary, "An Environmental LP", Audiocassette Tape, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 6)
    - Sorgen, Larry, "Look What They've Done to my Song", Audiocassette Tape, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified Student, "Dr. Kelly: Son of Fisherman", Audiocassette Tape, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified Student, "Interview with Tom O'Neill", Audiocassette Tape, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified Student, Untitled, Audiocassette Tape, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 10-12)
  - Ephemera, 4.822
    - Bag of dirt samples of unknown project, Undated
- Subject Files, 1964; 1966; 1968-1977; Undated; 5; 6.71 cubic ft.
  The files in this series vary in subject matter, but are all relevant to Lou Ismay's Environmental Forum classes and environmental issues. Many of the topics relate to environmental organizations. Other folders include news clippings and information by or about individual people, such as Ralph Nader, who visited and spoke at the school in the early 1970s. Included in this series is information on the Hudson River Sloop Restoration, which contains letters written by Pete Seeger. Oversized material is filed separately.
  - Accent on Research Office of Graduate Studies and Research, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Acronym, 1972 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Action for Children's Television, 1972 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Air Pollution, 1970 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Air Pollution, 1971-1974 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Air Pollution Study Guide, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Air Quality in the City of Albany, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Albany Area Environmental Coalition, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Albany County Short Range Recommendations, 1972-1977 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Albany From East Albany Sketch from 1872, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Albany Glass House Proposal, 1971 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Altamont Art, 1970 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - American Chemical Society Meeting in Toronto, 1970 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - The American Museum of Natural History, 1970 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - B-1 Bomber, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Benoit Emile A Survivalist Manifesto, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Bibliographies, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Bibliographies and Publications, 1974; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Bills and Receipts, 1973; 1975; 1976 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Biology 202 Lecture Topics, 1969 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Book and Publication Forms and Descriptions, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Boston Architectual Tour, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Building Prints, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - A Business and Society Review Interview, 1973 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Cadette Environment Badges, 1970 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Campus Environment, 1972 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Center for the Study of Science and Society SUNYA, 1970 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Centuries of Treasure 7th Grade English, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Circulating Material for Faculty, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Colloquium on Environmental Education, 1970 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Town of Colonie, 1972 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts Department of Natural Resources, 1972 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Congressional Voting Records on Environmental Issues, 1970 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Contacts Alphabetical Index Cards, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Contacts and Notes, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Contacts Organizational A-L, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Contacts Organizational M-Z, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Contacts and Source Lists, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Contacts, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4-5)
  - Cosmetics, 1970 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Costle, Douglas, Common Sense Talk About Agriculture and Environment, 1977 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Council on the Future, 1971 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - DEC Conservation Comments, 1975 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Dedicated Environmental Education for Posterity (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1971 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Dubin Fred's The New Architecture and Engineering, 1972 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Earth Week, 1972; 1973; 1976 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Earthday Activities, 1972 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Ebeneezer Howard Project, 1970 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - EDC Task Force, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Education as Mythology by M.I. Berger, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Edward Durell Stone & Associates SUNY SITE Plan, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Electric Utilities, 1970 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Elementary and Secondary Education Act Title 3, 1971 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - ENV 350 Land Use Survey, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - ENV 350B Environmental Study Project, 1975 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - ENV 405 Local Environment Planning and Protection, 1975 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Environment and Quality of Life, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Environment Party Platform, 1970 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Environment Technology and Valuer The Institute on Man and Science, 1970 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Environmental Act, 1973 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Environmental Concepts, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Environmental Concerns in Colleges around the U.S., 1970 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Environmental Conferences, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Environmental Conservation Commission Open Space and Coeymans, 1974 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Environmental Conservation Regions, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Environmental Decisions Commission, 1971-1973 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Environmental Disciplines and independent Study, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Environmental Education Center Delmar, NY, 1971 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Environmental Education Curriculum Development, 1970 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Environmental Education Directory, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Environmental intern Program, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Environmental Issues, 1969 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Environmental Leaders Forum, 1973 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Environmental Legislation, 1970 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Environmental Legislation, 1972-1974 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Environmental Legislation, 1973 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Environmental Legislation, 1975 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 45)